本视频中我们要讨论如何
For this part, we're going to discuss how to...
简单的创建一个项目 选择并下载你想要的CE版本
basically create a project and download the CRYENGINE version that you choose,
本视频中我们要下载CE V版本
which would be five.
然后我们将讨论如何从市场
And then also we will discuss how to go to the marketplace,
下载一个样本素材
install a sample asset
并在引擎中使用这个素材
and then get it up and runing inside of your engine.
所以有一堆东西需要介绍的 让我们开始吧
So we got a lot to cover, let's get to it.
刚开始 我们可以选择New Project 而且这里也显示“这里空空如也
To begin, we can click "New Project", it'll say "It's so empty in here
为何不创建个项目呢”
why don't you go on and create a project"
所以这两个按钮都可以创建项目
So it's the same thing as creating new one in both of these in which we can click.
So if I click that I go to the Create Project tab.
点下去后 会进入“新建项目”页面
在这里 我们有C++和C#
And in this, we have C++, we have C#.
在本教程中 我们选择C++
For this tutorial, we're just going to do C++
而目前我们只有CE 5.0版本
and we only have CRYENGINE 5 currently.
我们这里有空白模板项目
So we have a blank template
我们也有C#的东西
and then we also have the C# stuff.
这里我们就选择C++空白模板
So let's go ahead and just do the C++ blank template.
然后我们把这个项目命名 为 testProject
And we're going to choose it name it testProject.
然后我们要选择项目文件的存放位置
And now what we need to do is we need to choose the file location.
不像以前Steam版那样可以随便放
Unlike before with Steam we can go anywhere.
所以得选择个路径
So let's go ahead and choose a place.
我这里就选择D盘
Let's go on our system D:
然后新建个文件夹 命名为CRYENGINE_LAUNCHER
and then we'll go ahead and create a new folder and call this CRYENGINE_LAUNCHER.
选中这个文件夹 然后点OK
With that selected, we click OK.
现在我们就有了项目文件夹
So now we have the D:\CRYENGINE_LAUNCHER,
当然 你不一定非得放在D盘 可以放C盘或是任意盘符
this can be in the C drive or any other drive that you have.
但现在 我们还不能创建项目
And if we go, we can't actually create the project,
我们得选中"Blank" 才能创建
so we need to select the blank project to do so.
项目创建完后 它显示“需要下载引擎”
Once we create the project, it says "The engine download is required."
点击项目 它显示必须先下载引擎
So, to do so, if we click there it says we must download the engine first.
所以我们选择下载引擎
So let's download the engine,
点击上面这个图标 它会显示引擎已经开始下载
and if we go up top here, we click in here, we can notice that the engine is being downloaded.
它的下载时间取决于你的网速
Depending on your connection to the Internet, it may take a little while.
因为我在Crytek 所以它用不了多长时间
We've a faster connection here at the Crytek office,
所以我就先暂停录制 先等它下完
so I'm going to go ahead and pause this and wait for it to finish.
现在安装好了引擎 我们便可以用引擎打开我们的项目了
With the engine now installed, we're ready to go into CRYENGINE with our testProject.
通常要打开项目的话 直接点击就行了
In order to do so, we would normally just click on this tab.
但在这之前 我们先看下项目选项
Before doing anything, let's go over the options with testProject,
然后再进入编辑器
before jumping into the editor.
首先 我们可以编辑项目
First, we have here what we can edit the project,
这里可以修改引擎版本
this allows us to edit the engine version
以及项目名称 还可以删除项目
and also the name, plus we can remove the project.
返回去 点击下面的按钮 可以浏览项目文件夹
We go back, we can also click this botton which will reveal in the Explore.
它会弹出我们刚创建的CRYENGINE_LAUNCHER
If we look here, we have the CRYENGINE_LAUNCHER,
其中包含游戏的代码和资源
which has all of our code and our assets the game,
我们项目的所有文件都在这里
whatever our project is inside of this.
我们现在要做的是 点击这个项目 来打开它
So what we can do is now open this project by clicking,
然后它会在全新的CE界面中打开项目
and this will allow you to open the project inside the new CRYENGINE interface.
我先把启动器最小化
We're going to go ahead and minimize the launcher for the moment.
我们先创建一个关卡
And what we can do is go ahead and create a new level.
我把它命名为testProject
So let's do it in the testProject,
我要缩小地图尺寸 256x256 同样降低贴图尺寸
and I'm going to make it really small, 256, I'm gonna keep these texture as well
这样让它加载的更快
to allow us to launch it faster.
所以刚打开时 我们这什么都没有
So opening us up, we don't have anything,
因为这是C++空白模板项目
because this is the most blank install C++ we possibly can do.
我们现在打开启动器
And if we go into now the launcher.
我们准备从市场上下载一些素材资源
Now with everything installed, we're ready to go into the marketplace to get some assets.
所以我点击"MARKETPLACE"
So if I were to click on the marketplace,
然后会前往市场 选择"Residential Buildings"住宅楼
and go to the marketplace, so let's go ahead and click on "Residential Buildings".
然后我点"ADD TO CART"
What I can do is add to the cart.
这里显示已添加到购物车 然后我想立即结账
This will allow us to see that it's been added to the shopping cart, I want to check out now.
然后我选确认所有账户信息
So I'm gonna agree to all of my account information.
这里我选择同意服务条款
I'm also going to agree to the Terms of Service.
然后它显示购买完成
And it says that my purchase's been complete,
并且已被添加到启动器中
and it's been added to launcher.
所以我进入"My Assets"
So if I go to "My Assets",
这里会显示住宅楼素材
I can see something like my residential buildings,
然后我要安装它
and I want to install this.
下载过程就先略过了 也用不了多长时间
So let's go ahead and skip through it, it's not too long.
点击小三角图标 可以看见"Reveal in Explorer"
And if we click on this, we can see "Reveal in Explore".
我们有了这个资源pak文件
And now we have a pak file.
我们先把它复制
So let's go ahead and copy this.
然后回到项目那里 打开项目目录
And what we wanna do is go back to our project, let's reveal that.
如你所见 这里有个Assets文件夹
So we can see inside of here, we have assets,
我们创建一个...(口误)
so let's go ahead and create one...
(复制)一个pak文件
just with a pak file
复制刚下载的住宅楼素材
of the residential buildings we have.
所以Ctrl+C   Ctrl+V
So we press Ctrl+C Ctrl+V.
复制过去后 我们点击testProject
This inside of there, what we're going to do is click on the testProject
在引擎中打开项目
which would bring us into the engine.
先把启动器最小化
I'm gonna minimize the launcher.
Recent Files里就可以找到我们刚才的关卡
Already have a recent file, it's just a test project to get us in there.
因为是空项目 所以一堆Replace Me
We have the Replace Me, because it's a blank project.
我们点进Brush->Assets->objects
We go to the Brush, Assets, Objects.
现在就可以看见住宅楼素材
We can now see that we have our residential buildings.
我先拖进来一个木桶
So if I drag in my barrel,
按G键来放大
and I press the G key to frame up.
可以看见场景里有个木桶
We can see that we have a barrel on the scene.
直切重点 先进入环境编辑器
To quickly illustrate the point, let's go into the environment editor, maybe not make it.
时间调到中午12点 现在木桶看起来更好些
Twelve o'clock noon, we can see the barrel looks a bit better.
这个例子对任何CGF文件都适用
And this will be the case for any the CGF.
我们也有一些低模 如果你不想用
We also notice that we have some LODs, if you don't want to load those,
你可以直接用主模型
you strictly want to load main props.
我们就选个渔舍
If we go to our fishing house,
我们选fishing_house_a.cgf
we do fishing_house_a,
双击它 把它放在地图中
and by double-clicking, zoom out,
现在我们就有了渔舍
now we have the fishing house that
这种屋子通常出现在林地或森林关卡中
typically was speaking would be in the woodlands level or the forest level way back.
所以这就是 下载引擎 创建项目
So this is the process of just downloading some assets
获取素材 下载素材到项目里 的过程
inside of your new project after you download the engine, create your project,
并且这些素材是我们免费提供的
and got some assets that we provide for free.
希望你喜欢这期快速入门介绍
So I hope you enjoyed this quick starter pack introduction
对于创建并制作项目来说
as far as creating the projects and getting your stuff up and running.
在下个视频中 我们将深入介绍
We'll go into greater depth in another video
如何使用Game SDK
on how exactly to get GameSDK up and running.
这也是大家想直接切入的主题
Because that's gonna be what everybody wants to jump into
并使用孤岛危机3的游戏机制
and have all the mechanics from Crysis 3,
这样就能开始制作游戏
so they can build up, and maybe their engine
或者开发自己的游戏机制
or the mechanics for their own development step by step.
翻译：他出院了 花篝